<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>moodle on Dilawar's Blog</title><link>https://dilawar.github.io/tags/moodle/</link><description>Recent content in moodle on Dilawar's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dilawar.github.io/tags/moodle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Checking plagiarism in assignment (tested with VHDL language)</title><link>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2012/2012-03-05-checking-plagiarism-in-students-code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2012/2012-03-05-checking-plagiarism-in-students-code/</guid><description>I have developed some python scripts available here. I have used them in EE705 (VHDL, verilog) and found them very useful. It generates detailed log (which file matches which file) and sent emails to offenders with an archive of all file which were matched. It is integrated with my moodle-application (automatic download, extract, compare, sending-emails.) It also generates graphs (using python graph-tool) which shows the level of copying in the assignments.</description></item><item><title>Using Python to download submitted assignments from Moodle</title><link>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2012/2012-02-16-using-python-to-download-submitted-assignments-from-moodle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2012/2012-02-16-using-python-to-download-submitted-assignments-from-moodle/</guid><description>UPDATE : There are two version of this script. Output of both is same but they work on different version of moodle. This script (with configuration file available inside the repo) should work with new moodle while this one (with this configuration) should work with old moodle. Downloading each student&amp;rsquo;s assignment from moodle could be a real pain. I&amp;rsquo;ve updated my old scripts which download assignments from Moodle and stores each student&amp;rsquo;s assignment in a separate directory named after student.</description></item></channel></rss>