<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>language on Dilawar's Blog</title><link>https://dilawar.github.io/tags/language/</link><description>Recent content in language on Dilawar's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dilawar.github.io/tags/language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thinking about Languages</title><link>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2015/2015-02-03-thinking-about-languages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2015/2015-02-03-thinking-about-languages/</guid><description>“Don’t you see that the whole aim of Newspeak is to narrow the range of thought? In the end we shall make thoughtcrime literally impossible, because there will be no words in which to express it. Every concept that can ever be needed will be expressed by exactly one word, with its meaning rigidly defined and all its subsidiary meanings rubbed out and forgotten.” – 1984, George Orwell
It is hard to imagine how one can learn without some form of thinking available at one’s disposal.</description></item><item><title>What's there in Language?</title><link>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2010/2010-09-05-whats-there-in-language/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dilawar.github.io/posts/2010/2010-09-05-whats-there-in-language/</guid><description>Languages are not an easy thing to get curious about. The first time I got curious about languages was when I read about deconstruction in CAT exam preparatory material over which my room-mate was loosing sleep. Later it turns out that there are much more to a language than these school of thoughts.
Lets get curious about why language evolved in the first place. From the top of my mind, to woo a pretty girl by uttering something which does not make sense, to gain influence in a group by saying something which other would find impressive, to disseminate your ideologies.</description></item></channel></rss>